export const chapter = "Chapter - 8: FOOD FOR HEALTH";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What is the primary purpose of food according to the passage?",
          optionA: "Entertainment",
          optionB: "Growth and health",
          optionC: "Hydration",
          correctAnswer: "Growth and health",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is considered as body building food?",
          optionA: "Sugar",
          optionB: "Eggs",
          optionC: "Butter",
          correctAnswer: "Eggs",
        },
        {
          question: "What category does rice, chapati, and potato fall under?",
          optionA: "Protective food",
          optionB: "Energy giving food",
          optionC: "Body building food",
          correctAnswer: "Energy giving food",
        },
        {
          question: "Why is water important according to the passage?",
          optionA: "It helps in cooking",
          optionB: "It aids in digestion and waste elimination",
          optionC: "It is a body-building component",
          correctAnswer: "It aids in digestion and waste elimination",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the recommended daily intake of water mentioned in the passage?",
          optionA: "5-7 glasses",
          optionB: "8-10 glasses",
          optionC: "12-15 glasses",
          correctAnswer: "8-10 glasses",
        },
        {
          question: "Which meal is typically eaten between 1-2 pm?",
          optionA: "Breakfast",
          optionB: "Lunch",
          optionC: "Dinner",
          correctAnswer: "Lunch",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does the term 'protective food' refer to in the passage?",
          optionA: "Food that gives energy",
          optionB: "Food that promotes growth",
          optionC: "Food that prevents illness",
          correctAnswer: "Food that prevents illness",
        },
        {
          question: "According to good eating habits, what should one avoid?",
          optionA: "Fresh and clean food",
          optionB: "Junk food",
          optionC: "Fruits and vegetables",
          correctAnswer: "Junk food",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is emphasized regarding eating habits in the passage?",
          optionA: "Talking while eating",
          optionB: "Eating quickly",
          optionC: "Chewing food well and eating slowly",
          correctAnswer: "Chewing food well and eating slowly",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What should be done before and after every meal according to good eating habits?",
          optionA: "Exercise",
          optionB: "Wash hands",
          optionC: "Drink water",
          correctAnswer: "Wash hands",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "We need energy to do our daily activities. We get this energy from the ____ we eat. Food not only gives us energy but also helps us to grow and stay healthy and strong.",
          optionA: "Air",
          optionB: "Water",
          optionC: "Food",
          correctAnswer: "Food",
        },
        {
          question:
            "____ giving food includes rice, chapati, potato, butter, cheese, sugar etc.",
          optionA: "Body",
          optionB: "Energy",
          optionC: "Protective",
          correctAnswer: "Energy",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Food that helps us to grow and makes our bones and muscles strong is called ____ building food. Milk, eggs, pulses, peas, fish, etc. are some body building food items.",
          optionA: "Energy",
          optionB: "Protective",
          optionC: "Body",
          correctAnswer: "Body",
        },
        {
          question:
            "____ food, like fruits, vegetables, juices, nuts etc., protects us from falling sick or catching illness.",
          optionA: "Energy",
          optionB: "Protective",
          optionC: "Body",
          correctAnswer: "Protective",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Water is very important for us. It helps us to digest the food. It also helps us to throw out waste from the body. We should drink at least 8-10 glasses of water everyday.",
          optionA: "Enhancing",
          optionB: "Slowing down",
          optionC: "Aiding in",
          correctAnswer: "Aiding in",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Meal is the food that we eat at the fixed interval of time everyday. Breakfast at 8-9 am, Lunch at 1-2 pm, Evening snacks at 5-6 pm, Dinner at 8-9 pm.",
          optionA: "Irregular",
          optionB: "Fixed",
          optionC: "Variable",
          correctAnswer: "Fixed",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Always eat fresh and clean food. Eat all kinds of food in proper amount. Wash your hands before and after every meal. Eat slowly and chew the food well. Eat plenty of fruits and vegetables. Avoid eating junk food. Try not to talk while eating. Drink a lot of water everyday. Rinse your mouth after eating food.",
          optionA: "Talking while eating",
          optionB: "Eating quickly",
          optionC: "Chewing food well and eating slowly",
          correctAnswer: "Chewing food well and eating slowly",
        },
        {
          question:
            "To stay healthy, it is advised to ____ hands before and after every meal.",
          optionA: "Ignore",
          optionB: "Wash",
          optionC: "Dry",
          correctAnswer: "Wash",
        },
        {
          question:
            "One of the good eating habits is to eat slowly and ____ the food well.",
          optionA: "Spit out",
          optionB: "Chew",
          optionC: "Swallow",
          correctAnswer: "Chew",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What should be done before and after every meal according to good eating habits?",
          optionA: "Exercise",
          optionB: "Wash hands",
          optionC: "Drink water",
          correctAnswer: "Wash hands",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Eating slowly and chewing food well are considered good eating habits.",
          optionA: "Correct",
          optionB: "Incorrect",
          correctAnswer: "Correct",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Water is crucial for digestion and waste elimination from the body.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Milk, eggs, pulses, peas, and fish are examples of protective food items.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A meal is the food consumed at irregular intervals throughout the day.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Junk food is recommended for maintaining a healthy lifestyle.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The recommended daily water intake is 5-7 glasses.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The main responsibility of a receptionist at school is to teach students.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Fruits, vegetables, juices, and nuts are categorized as energy-giving foods.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A classroom typically has desks and chairs for students and a table and chair for the teacher.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Eating all kinds of food in proper amounts is a good eating habit.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
